- id: ckw-l09-2403
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - クリーム
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2439
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - オープン
  hint: "verbal noun (な-adj)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2448
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - デジタル
  hint: "noun (な-adj)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2451
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - バック
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2454
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - バッグ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2471
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - アドレス
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2484
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - パターン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2489
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ベスト
  hint: "noun (な-adj)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2489
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ボックス
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2495
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - フリー
  hint: "noun (な-adj)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2496
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - メッセージ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2504
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - プロジェクト
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2524
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - コーナー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2526
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - チャンス
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l09-2534
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - オブ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []
